

531 Main Road, Bismarck, ND 1357? b.griffin@myemail.com (420) 864\*2086 Professional and dependable taxi driver with over 5 years of experience providing high-quality transportation services for a ride-hailing company. Excellent geographical knowledge of Bismarck and the surrounding areas with an in-depth understanding of Local traffic avoidance. Friendly and informative interpersonal style with the ability to communicate key information on Local landmarks and amenities.

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### **TAXI DRIVER**

Potswork Drive, Bismarck, ND I March 2016 - Present

- Leverage paper maps and satellite navigation systems **to** find the quickest routes and avoid traffic, slashing the average journey time by 23% in 2020
- Present a positive company image and provide high-quality customer assistance, securing an average of \$2k of repeat custom per month
- Maintain a consistent satisfaction rating of at least 4,7 stars over three years
- · Provide sensitive support to customers with disabilities and Limited mobility

#### **DELIVERY DRIVER**

Spee-Dee Delivery Service, Bismarck, ND I July 2014 - March 2016

- Observed local traffic regulations, speed Limits, and safe driving practices, including driving in snowy and wet weather conditions
- Performed routine vehicle maintenance and safety checks and kept the interior clean and tidy
- Managed time effectively to make 98% of deliveries before the set deadline
- Communicated clearly with the control center to update them on delays or incidents that may affect deliveries or other fleet drivers

## **EDUCATION**

HIGH SCHOOL DIPLOMA

Century High School, Bismarck, ND I June 2013

### **KEY SKILLS**

- Customer service
- Route planning
- · Satnav systems
- Road safety
- · Vehicle maintenance
- Communication skills

## **CERTIFICATIONS**

 North Dakota Commercial Driver's License, July 2013